《越狱》前情回顾
Previously on prison break
我要逃出去
I'm breaking out,
必须利用你确保我哥能和我一起走
and you're going to make sure my brother goes with me.
对不起 亨利
I'm sorry, Henry.
这消息是留给玛丽克鲁斯的
This message is for Maricruz.
我一定会在伊克斯塔巴的机场等你
I'll be there in the airport in Ixtapa waiting for you.
苏克雷 沿着路一直向南
Sucre, down the road,
如果碰到麻烦
if you're in trouble,
就在留言板上留言
post a note on the message board.
网址是什么?
What's it called?
Europeangoldfinch.net
是一种鸟 对吧?
That's a bird, right?
去收拾你们的东西
Go pack your things.
我们这就出发
We're moving.
我们会成为一家人的
We will be a family
死也要在一起
if it kills us.
要是停下来 那你就半途而废了
Pull this off and you're halfway home.
你一定记得家里的样子吧
You remember what home is like, don't you?
别碰我家人!
Stay away from my family!
她得吃药
She needs that medicine
没药她坚持不了两天
she can't go two days without it.
好难受
I don't feel good.
哦 亲爱的...
Oh, sweetie...
迈克尔 我想要这一切结束
Michael, I want for this to be over.
对我俩来说都是如此
That makes two of us.
唯一的问题是要弄清  你父亲留给你的到底是什么
It's just a question of looking at whatever it is your father gave you.
只有一把钥匙
It's just a key.
那个上锁的盒子就在这家雪茄俱乐部里
It's in a lockbox at the corona de oro cigar club.
我不是逃犯 没那么显眼  把钥匙给我
I'm not a wanted fugitive. Give me the key.
我去拿
I'll do it.
想要散散步么?
You want to take a walk?
唐克雷蒂小姐
Miss Tancredi?
我需要和你谈一下
I need to have a word with you.
唐克雷蒂小姐
Miss Tancredi?
当然可以
Of course.
唐克雷蒂小姐?  女士?
Miss Tancredi? Ma'am?
唐克雷蒂小姐
Miss Tancredi?
得走了
it's time to go.
女士
Ma'am?
他们从后门走了
They're going out the back.
快点 快
come on, come on.
注意  航班抵达...
MINNEAPOLIS, NINNESOTA NINNEAPOLIS/ST.Paul INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
请帮我接儿科
Pediatrics, please.
你好
Hello.
卡梅伦
Cameron.
你好 爸爸
Hi, dad.
你怎么样啊? 大家伙
How are you doing, big guy?
我很好 在吃午饭呢
Good.I'm eating my lunch.
好吃吗?
How is it?
太难吃了
Pretty disgusting.
你妈妈可能会从家里给你带晚餐来的
Maybe your mom can bring you some dinner from home.
今天看医生了么?
Did you see the doctor today?
是的 他说只要我不去街上跑
Yeah.He said I can go home this week
这个星期我就可以回家了
as long as I stay out of the street.
你是个聪明的大男孩
You're a smart young man.
你是知道怎样过街的
You know how to cross the street.
你生我的气么?
Are you mad at me?
听我说
Listen to me.
没有人生你的气
No one is mad at you.
这不是你的错
And this wasn't yo fault.
我本应该照顾好你的
I'm the one who should have been looking out for you.
可你那时不在的
You weren't even there.
但我本该在的
But I should have been.
唉 真是的
Aw, man.
喂  儿子  我得挂电话了
Hey, buddy, listen.I got to go,
我稍后再打给你  好么?
but I'll call you back later, okay?
- 好吧  再见  - 卡梅伦...
- Okay.Bye.  - Cameron...
我爱你
I love you.
卡...?
Cam?
我是
Yeah.
有没有富兰克林的消息?
What have we got on Franklin?
从早上起一直没有新消息
Nothing new since this morning.
明尼苏达餐厅抢劫案的另一个目击证人
Another witness from the Minnesota diner robbery
确认了疑犯的身份
gave a positive I.D.
很好  15分钟前我刚到明尼阿波利斯
Good. 'Cause I just landed in Minneapolis 15 minutes ago.
其他消息呢?
Anything else?
那个女孩子  迪迪
Yeah. The girl. Dede.
很明显她生病了  是某种慢性疾病
Apparently, she's been ill,some chronic condition.
把富兰克林的面部照片 发传真给明尼苏达东南区的各大医院
Fax Franklin's mug shot to every hospita in southeastern Minnesota.
已经做了  运气好的话
Already done.With any luck,
那女孩不得不去医院治疗 那么他就会现身了
she'll get sick enough to need one, then he'll show his face.
你还没有孩子  是吧  兰?
You don't have kids, do you, Lang?
没
Nope.
有其他消息再通知我
Call me when you have something else.
买这个
I'll take that.
- 没拿到  - 什么?
- We didn't get it. - What?
我们稍后还得再回去
And we need to get back in there soon.
一旦他们发现莎拉去过那里
Once the company finds out Sara was in there,
用不了多久他们就会怀疑的
it won't be long before they start wondering why.
你们找个靠近俱乐部的地点  躲好
Find a spot close to the club and sit tight.
我们要用车
We're going to take the car.
- 几个小时后回来  - 你们去哪?
- We'll be back in a couple of hours.- Where you going?
有个会员也许能帮我们
Turns out that maybe there's one member of the club who can help us.
谁?
Who?
波普?
Pope?
请稍等
Just a minute.
亨利
Henry.
你来这做什么?
What are you doing here?
你在保释期逃走
Aside from jumping bail
还四处躲避警察?
and evading the authorities?
有些事我要和你说清
There's something that you need to hear,
但是首先我想知道  你是否会听
but, first, I need to know if you'll listen.
莎拉  我可以明确的告诉你  没什么好谈的
I can assure you, Sara, we've got nothing to discuss.
先生  求你了  只要5分钟
Sir, please.I need five minutes.
5分钟过后  你要我们走  我们一定走
After that, if you want us to, we'll leave.
还有谁?
Who's "us"?
我不想惹麻烦
I don't want any trouble.
很好 我们也不想
Good.Because that's not why we're here.
你到底想干什么?
What the hell are you thinking about,
来这儿跳华尔兹? 你是个通缉犯!
waltzing in here? You're a wanted criminal!
你可能忘记了
In case you've forgotten,
我忠于一生的职责就是
I dedicated my career--my entire life--
把你们这样的人关在监狱里
to keeping people like you behind bars.
你指的是有罪的人
You're talking about guilty people.
我哥哥是无辜的
My brother is innocent.
我们很有可能找到证据  证明这点
And we may have the evidence to prove it.
我不在乎什么证据  你们走吧
Well, I don't care; I want you out of here.
证据在科罗纳德奥俱乐部的一个锁柜里
It's in a lockbox at the corona del oro club,
你是那里的会员
and you're a member.
出去!
Out!
亨利 请听我说
Henry, please listen.
莎拉 我本来以为你更明白事理
Sara, I'm tempted to say you should have known better.
但你的所作所为...
But after what you did...
我父亲是在调查布伦斯的案子时
my father was looking into the burrows case
被谋杀的
when he was murdered.
这把钥匙 是我从他尸体上唯一找到的东西
This key is the only thing I could recover from his body.
我们去哪儿?
Where are we going?
他们都饿了
They're hungry.
我们开了一整天车
We've been driving all day.
吃块奶糖
Chick-o-stick.
他们需要吃饭
They need real food.
这不是到了吗 亲爱的
Soon enough, pumpkin.
他妈的!
Alackaday.
一群恶棍 流氓 土匪和强盗
Miscreants.Defilers. Defacers.Despoilers.
这是哪儿?
What is this?
我家
My home.
不!
Aw, no, no, no!
不
No.
拜托 拜托
********************
你去哪儿
Where you headed?
机场
Airport
你真走运
You're in luck.
要多久?
How far is it?
二十分钟左右  赶飞机?
Twenty minutes. Catching a flight?
我女朋友四点的飞机
My girl's on the four o'clock flight.
应该没问题
Shouldn't be a problem.
好极了
Good.
我是卡德纳
Cadena here.
你还差多远?
How close are you?
二十英里
Twenty miles.
知道了
Roger that.
怎么了?
What was that?
没事 我是机场保安
I'm airport security.
有美国逃犯非法入境  尽是这种事儿
American fugitive's flying in, something like that.
好 宝贝 乖乖坐在这儿 好不好?
All right, sweetie, why don't you sit over here, okay?
好的
All right.
我到那边去一下
I'm going to go over there
去跟那位女士谈谈
and I'm going to talk to the lady.All right?
你想要什么吗?
You need anything?
确定?
You sure?
好
Okay.
什么事?
Yes?
我女儿迪迪病得很重
My daughter, Dede, she's really sick.
她的肾脏一直不太好 从...
She's had this kidney thing since she,
从...很小的时候起
she was real young.
- 大概有... - 她在哪儿?
- It's mostly... - Where is she?
就在那儿
She's sitting right there.
你们之前来过吗?
Have you been here before?
没有 我从外地来的
No.I'm from out of town.
能看下你的社保卡吗?
Can I see your insurance card?
不行
Um...no, no.
我没上任何保险
I don't have any insurance.
我离开军队以后 社保就被停掉了
After I left the army, they discontinued my insurance.
你们是亨内平郡居民吗?
Are you a resident of Hennepin county?
我说了 我们从外地来
Like I said, we're from out of town.
你有驾照吗?
You have a driver's license?
听着 我没有驾照
Look, I don't have a driver's license,
没有社保卡 或其他类似的东西
an insurance card,or anything like that,
但我懂得法律
but I do know the law.
你必须给我女儿看病
You have to see my little girl.
我得问问主管
Let me go get my supervisor.
很好
Good.
你们兄弟的事与我无关
I don't give a rat's ass about you or your brother.
我曾经信任你
I trusted you,
我关心照顾你  如同对待我自己的儿子一般
I took you under my wing,I treated you like my own son.
我是那么相信你!
I believed you!
日复一日  你却在骗我
Day after day, you lied to me.
你说这到底个是什么样的人?
What kind of a man does that?
一个绝望的人
A desperate one.
好...
Yeah.
你们来真是个天大的错误
you two made a big mistake coming here today.
你们让我别无选择
You give me no choice.
我要通报当局
I'm going to notify the authorities right now.
对不起...
I'm sorry...
...我不能让你这样做
but I can't let you do that.
我不想伤害你  亨利
I don't want to hurt you, Henry.
你用枪指着我还这么说
Said by the man with the gun.
这可能是唯一能使你信任我的方法
If it's the only way I can convince you, so be it.
你这样做并不能使我信任你
Well, you're not going to convince me by doing that.
我并不是你想象的那种人
I'm not the man you think I am.
是啊  但我确实知道你是什么样的人  迈克尔
Yeah, well, I have a pretty good idea who you are, Michael.
如果你知道的话
If that's true,
你就应该明白  我根本不想去福克斯河监狱
then you already know I never wanted to be in fox river.
也没有想到会遇见你  亨利
I never wanted to meet you, Henry.
我更没有想过去毁掉你的生活
I certainly didn't want to ruin your life.
对  很好  你做得很棒
Yeah.Well, you've done a pretty damn good job.
- 请你不要和他说这些  - 我的话还没讲完
- You're not saying anything to him - I haven't said myself,
亨利  我也一直在调查这些事
Henry.I've looked into this.
他说的都是千真万确的
What he's saying to you is absolutely true.
我只是想挽救哥哥的性命
I just want my brother's life back.
并且让人们知道真相
I want people to know the truth.
我会不惜一切代价
I'd give anything for that.
甚至是我的生命
I'd lay down my life.
是啊  你站在枪的那一边
Well, that's easy for you to say,
当然可以这么说
standing on that side of the gun.
那么这样又如何
What if I'm standing on this side?
你可以到别的地方去问问
There are places that can better serve your needs.
我知道我的权利
Look, I know my rights, okay?
这里不是基础护理站
This isn't a primary care facility.
我们是对有生命危险状况
We provide necessary care
提供必要的治疗
in life-threatening situations.
我知道你想说什么了
Look, I know what this is
你们要等到她危在旦夕了再来伸出援助之手?
are you going to wait until she's dead before you give her some help?
这就是你想告诉我的?!
Is that what you're telling me?!
我不想为这事和你争吵
I'm not going to argue with you, sir.
这里是医院  不是避难所
This is a hospital, not a homeless shelter.
你说什么?
A what?
你刚才和我说什么?
What did you just say to me?
我真不敢相信你们是这样的人
I can't believe you people.
我们走
Come on.
这儿人太多了 我们走吧
The line is a little bit too long, okay?
我们去别的地方
We'll go somewhere else.
我们要去哪儿?
Where are we going?
我们去找其他医生  宝贝
We got to find another doctor, sweetie.
我的天
Oh, my god.
我们走
Let's go.
闪开!
Move!
快  宝贝!
Come on, baby.
富兰克林!
Franklin!
都闪开!
Move out of the way!
FBI! 站住!
FBI! Stop!
站住!
Stop!
好吧
Okay.
宝贝  放开我好吗?  你下来
Just one second, baby. Baby, you got to get down, okay?
别这样  宝贝
No, no, sweetie, you got to get dowN.
好孩子  放开他
You got to let him go, honey.
下来
Get down.Get down.
好孩子  你要放开他
Honey, you got to let him go.
不
No.
她不肯放开我
Man, she's not letting go.
别让她为你犯的错 付出代价
Don't let her pay for your mistakes.
你明白我的意思吗?
you hear me?
现在向你开枪  我不会有一丝犹豫
I could shoot you right now and not even think twice.
但你做不到
But you won't.
你在监狱部门那么多年 不能这样轻易抛开你的人生
You spent too much time around prisons to throw your life away like that.
你到底想怎么样?
What the hell are you trying to pull?
很简单-- 这把钥匙
It's simple--that's the key
能让一个无罪的人 得到自由
to an innocent man's freedom.
求你了  亨利
Come on, Henry.
我们都知道发生了什么
We both know there's something going on here.
许多人为此而送命
Too many people have died.
看着我的眼睛  你会明白此刻我没有丝毫的掩饰
Look me in the eye, tell me you don't believe there's a cover-up going on right now.
我没有义务这么做  迈克尔
I've got no moral obligations here, Michael.
据我所知 林肯罪不可恕
As far as I know, Lincoln is as guilty as hell.
那我们一起去查个究竟
Then take a ten-minute drive with me,and we'll find out.
我就这一个请求
That's all I ask.
亨利  你是知道的
Henry, you've looked into this before.You've thought about it.
是的
I have.
我很清楚一点
And I've come to one conclusion--
我和此事无关
this has nothing to do with me.
我懂得法律
but I am a man of the law,
而且我有必要告发
and right now,I've got a convicted felon
这个就站在我家的重犯
standing inside my house
也许我能和你做笔交易
Well, maybe there's something I can offer you
来改变你的想法
to make you change your mind.
你想怎么处置我们?
What do you intend to do with us?
你个汽车修理工
You grease monkey.
你都不配拿最低工资
You don't deserve minimum wage.
我他妈又不在墓地工作
The hell i don't, working graveyard.
没有谁配拿到多于每小时一美元的钱
There ain't no man deserve more pennies on a dollar per hour
因为那比他们的智商指数还高
than they got iq points in their head.
我又不傻
I ain't stupid.
好像跟其余的人差不多傻吧
Seems equal stupid as the rest of you.
骨子里好像都差不多
Seems to run in the genes.
泰迪
Teddy.
十个同义词
Ten symonyms.
选一个词
Pick a word.
毁灭
Destroy.
十个"毁灭"的同义词
Ten synonyms for "destroy".
废除
Annul.
损伤
Mutilate.
消灭
Liquidate.
废止
Abrogate.
消除 毁坏
Quell.Ravage.
消毁
Expunge.
破坏
Demolish.
根除
Extirpate.
破灭
Extinguish.
听到了吗?!
Whoo, you see that?
傻?  哥们
Stupid, my pail,
我儿子将来会当总统的
my boy's gonna be president.
你怎么没
How come you ain't
学习?
studying?
因为我累了
'Cause I'm tired.
因为我觉得自己就像一只马戏团的猴子一样
'Cause I feel like a circus freak.
这样...
Well...
现在...
now...
你要以它为最大的兴趣
it's in your own best interest.
懂吗?
Don't you understand that? Hmm?
总有一天你会当上总统的
Now, you're going to be president someday.
记住我的话
You mark my words.
西奥多
Theodore.
西奥多 你听到了吗?
Theodore, do you hear me?
你想如何处置我们?
What are you going to do with us?
我们要彻底结束一些东西
We're gonna put down some roots.
你要我死 保罗
You wanted me dead, Paul.
只是执行命令
Just following orders.
为根本不是我做的事  而把我送上电椅
Sent me to the chair for something I didn't do,
一切都是为了你的总统
all for your president.
你可真是心甘情愿
You were willing to do that.
只是...执行...命令
Just... following... orders.
斯蒂德曼说你爱她
Steadman said you loved her.
斯蒂德曼疯了 他被禁闭在牢笼里
Steadman was a deranged man that lived in a locked box.
你不会爱上一个
You don't love someone
爱权力胜过爱生活的人
that loves power more than life.
很痛苦 对吗?
Bitter, huh?
我有吗?
Am I?
无意冒犯
No offense,
但是要体会这样的关系
but you're not capable of
你还不够格
understanding the relationship.
好 不管你怎么看
Okay, any way you look at it,
这事不会有幸福结局
there is no light at the end of this tunnel.
无论如何
One way or another,
你和我 大家都将难免一死
you and I, we die.
你弟弟也一样
Your brother, too.
那是他为你做的一切带来的耻辱
Which is a shame given all he's done for you.
我有个妹妹 在15年里没有跟她说过一句话
I have a sister I haven't talked to in 15 years.
你认为她过得很好?
Think she's better off for it?
我们会做到的
We'll make it.
那是什么 信仰?
What is that, faith?
是的 那是信仰
Yeah, that's faith.
我看到的一切只是一个黑洞
All I see is a black hole.
迟早会把我们一个个都吞掉
And sooner or later, they are going to suck each one of us into it.
但是当他们要置我死地时
But when they come for me,
我定会多拉几个跟我陪葬
I'm going to take as many of them with me as I can.
她肯定伤透你的心了 保罗
She must have really broken your heart, Paul.
昨晚 莱娜斯总统出席了 一个芝加哥募捐会
President Reynolds attended a Chicago fund raiser last night
这将是她两天内在这个 多风的城市里的其中一项行程
as part of her two-day stop in the windy city.
莱娜斯的受欢迎度 在中西部继续飙升
Reynolds' popularity continues to soar in the midwest with
她将在这个星期内陆续
appearances scheduled in Indianapolis,
到访印第安纳州 底特律 和密歇根州的弗林特
Detroit and Flint,Michigan later in the week.
在一个民主党募捐活动...
At a democratic fundraiser...
金先生
Mr. Kim...
莎拉 唐克雷蒂  在芝加哥出现了
Sarah Tancredi surfaced in Chicago.
一个小时前有人发现她在科罗纳德奥俱乐部
She was spotted at the coronadeoro club about an hour ago.
科罗纳德奥俱乐部?
Coronadeoro club?
是一个雪茄俱乐部
It's a cigar club.
她的父亲曾是那里的会员
Her father was a member.
他持有一个私人的雪茄盒
He kept a private humidor there.
给我备专机飞往芝加哥
Get me a jet to Chicago.
我..要和你道别了
Hey, I got to, split.
总站在那边啊
terminal's this way
我得..去趟厕所
Yeah, um, gotta hit the bathroom.
总站那边也有啊
There's one in the terminal.
是吗...不用了
Really, man, thanks.
谢谢你的顺风车
Thanks for the ride
你带了你的武器吗?
Got your sidearm?
很有可能会用得上 这是我们要找的人
May need it. Here is our guy.
他现在就在这!
He's here
你不会真的以为他会来见你吧?
tell me you're not still thinking he's going to show.
他让你失望这么多次
He's let you down so many times.
你也知道的
You know that.
那可能是我肚里的孩子在告诉我
Yeah, well, maybe it's the baby in me
这一次不会像从前那样
that's telling me that this time it's going to be different.
我并不想打破你的幻想
I don't mean to burst your bubble,
但他是不会来了
but he's not going to show.
幻想没有破灭
Bubble's not burst.
我有三个字要对你说
I got three words for you.
嗯？
Yeah?
马上跑
We gotta run.
特丽莎 很高兴见到你！
Good seeing you, Theresa!
快点
你能来我太高兴了！
I'm so glad you came.
这太疯狂了
You're crazy.
他们怎么知道的?
How did they know?
你确定...
You're certain...
雪茄盒里的是什么东西？
about what's in the box?
不确定  但我们只有这条路可走了
No, but it's all we've got.
谢谢你  亨利
Thank you, Henry.
你有把握吗？
You sure about this?
没有
No.
不管怎样
Either way,
你还欠我一顿晚餐
you still owe me dinner.
是吗？
Is that so?
没错  你在福克斯河监狱的第一个星期
Yeah.First week in fox river,
曾向我许诺  如果有一天
you promised me,
你从那里出去  你会请我共进晚餐
if you ever got out of there, you'd take me to dinner.
这样吧  这件事办妥后
Well, maybe, after we wrap this up,
送波普回去的路上 我会找个地方  请你吃面卷饼的
we can stop off and get you a burrito on the way back to Pope's house.
斯科菲尔德  我不知道你喜欢什么
Scofield, I don't know what you're used to,
不过要是没有小腓厉牛排
but anything short of a filet mignon
我是不会满意的
is not going to cut it with me.
那就这么说定了
It's a date.
给我电话
喂
Hey.
你是怎么办到的?
How did you pull that off?
我待会儿再向你解释
I'll tell you later.
-他进去了没有  -进去了
-Is he in yet?  -Yep.
这应该不会很久 最多几分钟
This shouldn't take more than a couple of minutes.
要是时间拖久了 那我们肯定有麻烦
Any longer than that, we'll know we've got trouble.
这边请
This way.
谢谢
Thank you.
波普先生
Mr. Pope.
嗨  沃伦  还好吧？
Hey, Warren, how's it going?
你听说今天早晨的事了吗？
Did you hear what happened this morning?
莎拉  唐克雷蒂竟然来了
Sara Tancredi came in.
嗯  我听说了
Yeah.So I heard.
下次  别让她再跑了
Next time, don't let her get away.
谢了
Thanks.
对不起  打扰下
Excuse me, do you mind
我能否借你的电脑一用
if I borrow your computer for a moment?
没问题
No problem.
谢谢
Thanks.
孩子们 帮忙收拾下啊
Pitch in, chitlins!
我们不能这么做
We can't do this.
我们不能住这儿
We can't live here.
是啊  像这样当然不行
No, of course not like this.
我们得打扫下  我们现在就打扫
We gonna clean.We are cleaning!
我们要重建这个地方
We gonna rebuild!
你不能对他们这么做
You can't do this to them.
看看他们
Look at them.
你们不介意到这边待一会儿吧
You all mind coming along here for a minute.
快过来
Come on.
我没必要再拿枪
I think we're past me waving that gun around,
对吗
don't you think?
快
Come on.
很好
Thank you.
你想干嘛
What are you doing?
他们不会有事的
Nothing is gonna happen to them.
苏珊 我亲爱的苏珊
Susan. Susie Q.
你以为我把你带到这儿来
Do you think I'd bring you here to
来到这个对我而言如此神圣的地方
so sacred a place to me as this
如果我想伤害你
if I meant you ill?
看着我
Look at me!
我真的不是你想象中那样的禽兽
I am not the animal you think you see before you.
我在承担别人犯错而带来的报应
I am the laws of karma all come down wrong.
难道你不明白吗
Don't you understand?
我不懂
I don't.
我想说的是...
What I'm trying to say is that...
我是我父亲造的孽
I am the sin of my father.
你为什么告诉我这些
Why are you telling me this?
因为我爱你
Because I love you.
因为我希望你能理解我
Because I want you to understand me.
我是巴格威尔家族的最后一代
I am the last in the line of Bagwells.
这堕落家族的最后一代
The tail end of a corrupted breed.
感谢上帝
The earth, thank god,
这世上再也不会有巴格威尔家的后代了
shall see no more of our generations.
我不能生育  苏珊
I cannot procreate, Susan.
不过也正因如此
And yet,
我有了巨大的希望
there's something in that that gives me great hope.
再也不会有叫巴格威尔的人 在这世上闲逛了
No more Bagwells shall roam this planet.
流淌在他们血脉中的卑劣品性 也将不复存在
Not with that vile blood in their veins.
我想做的就是
All I want to do is
断绝这个血脉  毁灭它
end the bloodline,extirpate it,
然后重新开始
and start another,a fresh.
一个新的家族
A new family.
哦 泰迪
Oh, Teddy.
这些孩子是我的救星
Those children are my salvation,
是我让这个世界变得更好的机会
my chance to make this world a better place.
我会变好的 苏珊
I will be good, Susan.
我会爱他们
I will love them.
我会爱你
I will love you.
我会参加教会
I will take communion,
在圣光的照耀下  接受洗礼
be baptized under a truer light.
我唯一的请求
All I ask is
就是要你重新爱我
that you love me back,
只要一点点
just a little.
或者慢慢的学会这么做
Or learn to do so in time.
你能做到吗 苏珊
Can you do that, Susan?
我不能
I can't.
对不起
I'm sorry.
泰迪
Teddy.
妈妈
Mommy.
求你了 求你了
Please, please.
泰迪 好吧 我答应你
Teddy, it's okay, it's okay.
泰迪
Teddy.
泰迪 求你了
Teddy, please.
泰迪
Teddy
泰迪 对不起
Teddy, I'm sorry.
我能做到
I can do it.
我能爱你
I can love you.
我们在哪
Where are we?
宝贝 我们在医生的办公室
At the doctor's office, sweetie.
喂 我这里有急诊
Hello, I have an emergency in here.
有人吗
Hello?
你好
Hello.
你是医生吗
Hey, you the doctor?
你需要排队等
Need to wait your turn.
不 现在就轮到我了 我有急诊
No, it is my turn.This is an emergency right here.
我需要你看看我的女儿 行吗
I need you to look at my daughter, okay?
她不舒服
She's not feeling too good.
拜托了
Please.
宝贝 抱好了 这样我好...
Sweetie, hold on, so I can...
好吧  这是我所有的钱了  可以吗?
all right, look, this is all the money I got, okay?
这是400美金
That's $400.
请您看看我女儿
Please look at my daughter.
她怎么了?
What's the matter with her?
她患有肾病...多囊肾
She has a kidney disease...PKD
以前我们都能把她的病情控制住
Normally, we have it under control,
但现在我不希望看到的事情还是发生了
but I don't like what I'm seeing right now.
他的胃也开始疼了
Her stomach hurts, okay?
而且高烧不断
And she's always hot.
-她的食欲怎么样  -一点都不好
-How's her appetite?  -It's gone.
而且很容易疲劳  是吗 宝贝儿?
She's always tired, ain't that right, baby?
好的
All right.
让她躺这
Hop up here.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了
Okay.
让医生帮你好好检查一下 好吗？
He just wants to take a good look at you, okay?
可能需要做很多的检测
May need to run a few tests.
大夫  你尽管去做好了
Just do what you have to do, man.
我一会就回来
I'm gonna be right here,
好吗  宝贝儿?
okay, baby?
恩
Okay.
现在进展的怎么样了?
What's going on now?
还在那儿
Still in there.
时间太久了
This is taking too long.
等  等  等
Wait, wait, wait.
他出来了
Here he comes.
出什么事了?
What's happening?
不速之客来了
We got company.
你好  亨利
Hello, Henry.
没想到你也抽雪茄啊
I didn't know you were a cigar man.
你是谁?
Who are you?
呃  一个朋友
Uh, a friend.
更确切的说是  同事
A colleague, in fact.
我们都是执法工作者
We're both in law enforcement.
我已经不是了
I'm not anymore.
是啊
That's right.
你么  已经退休了
You're, uh, retired.
-你认识他?  -是的
-Know the guy?  -Yeah.
看上去  结束工作后
Looks like the lifestyle's treating you well.
你过的还挺自在
Yeah?
喝着白兰地酒  抽着古巴雪茄?
Socializing over cubans and cognac?
但事实并非如此  是吧?
But that's not what you were doing, is it?
亨利
Henry.
你不介意让我看一下你的口袋吧?
You don't mind if ask you to empty your pockets?
但事实上我介意
As a matter of fact, I do.
我不想和你玩游戏
I'm not going to play any games with you.
我们都很明白你为什么会到这儿来
We both know why you came here today.
年青人  我希望你能把路让开
I suggest you get out of my way, young man.
不可以
I can't do that.
除非你希望
Unless you'd like to
你和你的家人都有麻烦
cause serious trouble for yourself and your family,
我建议你应该把你找到的东西交给我
I advise you to hand over whatever it is you found.
快
Now.
迈克尔
Michael?
上车!
Get in!
我们走!
Let's go!
林肯  快!
Linc!
莎拉!
Sara!
没事了  没事了
Whoa, whoa, it's okayit's okay.
别紧张  没事了
Easy, easy, it's okay, it's okay.
太太  你还好吗?
Ma'am, are you all right?
你们怎么会来
I don't understand.
我们接到了电话
We got a call.
有人说这里有人质
Someone said there's a hostage situation here.
没人知道我们在这儿
No one knew we were here.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
好了
Okay.
结果如何?
Hey, so what's going on?
恐怕你的女儿出现了肾衰竭的迹象
I'm afraid your daughter shows signs of renal failure.
她以前做过血液透析吗?
She ever had hemodialysis?
没...  没有
No, hemo... no.
不会到这种地步吧
No, this has never really gone that far.
什么  你打算就在这里做吗?
What, are you planning on doing it right here?
我们没有相关设施
Were not set up for it.
她也没有准备
And neither is she.
但是不远的几条街区外
But there is a county
有一家郡级透析中心
dialysis clinic a few blocks away.
我现在要在她的颈部插入导管
But we're gonna have to place a catheter in her neck
以便她接受进一步诊断
so she can be examined.
忍着点  宝贝  可能会有一点凉
Hold on, sweetie, this is gonna be a little cold.
没事的  孩子
It's okay, baby.
等一下  等一下
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait. Wait,
这是什么?
what, what is that?
套管针
It's a trocar.
是插导管用的
It's used for placing the catheter.
宝贝  躺下
I got her.
真的有必要这样么?
Do we really have to go this far?
听我说
Look.
我现在尽我所能做到最好
I'm doing the best I can here,
还有你要明白的是
but you got to understand something.
你的女儿现在病了
Your daughter is sick.
也许这手段看上去很严重  但情况就是如此
Now, this may look like a desperate measure because it is.
可能会有一点疼
This is gonna hurt a little bit.
住手!
Stop!
住手
Stop.
过来  孩子
Come on, baby.
我们走了
Come with me.
我做不到
I can't do this.
怎么了?
What's going on?
我和波普做了一个交易
I made a deal with Pope.
你和波普做了一个交易?
You made a deal with Pope?
什么交易?
What kind of deal?
如果他跟我们走  然后能拿到我们要的东西
If he came with us and if we got what we needed,
我就去自首
I said I'd turn myself in.
什么?!
What?
我们都不知道那东西究竟是什么!
We don't even know what this thing is!
迈克尔  也许那东西根本没用
It could be nothing, Michael.
你知道这事?
You know about this?
刚才他开口说  我才知道
Not until it came out of his mouth.
这是我能想到的唯一办法
It's the only thing I could think of.
还有你们两个在 这一切依然能够结束
You two can still finish this.
没有我  你们也必须做到
You'll just have to do it without me.
我不会让你这么做的  迈克尔
I'm not gonna let you do this, Michael.
别...
Just...
如果你去  再也不能回头了
there's no coming back from this.
等等
Hold on.
怎么了?
What's the hold up?
你哥哥说得对
Your brother's right.
我没法指望法庭
I wouldn't count on the courts
会对此事给你宽大处理
to show you any leniency in this.
那不要紧
That doesn't matter.
我说过我会信守承诺  完成交易
I said I'd hold up my end of the deal.
你已经做到了
You already did.
我听了这个
I listened to this.
这里面有你需要的东西
You have something here.
肯定有许多人不希望你拿到它
There's gonna be a lot of people who wish you didn't,
现在你拿好它
but you do.
听我说  亨利...
Listen, Henry...
我要是你  我现在就走
I'd go now if I were you.
别认为这是宽恕
And don't consider this forgiveness.
因为再过十秒钟  我就会改变主意
In fact, I'm about ten seconds away from changing my mind.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了...
Okay...
听我说...
here, listen...
让我帮你把帽子戴上 好吗?
let's tuck you in, all right?
来  我们走
Come on. Let's go.
我们...
Let's just...
我们再多呆一会儿  好吗
let's just sit for a bit longer, okay?
我们一会再走  好吗
We're gonna go in a little bit, okay?
你明白爸爸全心的爱你胜过一切  对不对
You know daddy loves you with all his heart, right?
爸爸深深地爱着你
I love you so much.
爸爸对不起你  孩子  爸爸对不起你...
I'm so sorry.
我真的很抱歉 宝贝
I'm so sorry, baby.
什么事
Yeah.
你有个电话
Got a call for you.
我稍后再打过去
I'll call back.
我刚收到来自北边一诊所的消息
I just heard from some clinic up north.
他们在一小时前接触过富兰克林
They had contact with Franklin a half an hour ago.
我想你会想要接听这个电话的
I think you want to take this.
帮我接通
Put it through.
我是马宏 你是谁？
Yeah? Mahone.
你是负责人？
Is this the man in charge?
对
Oh, yeah.
我的名字是
My name...
本杰明 迈尔斯 富兰克林
is Benjamin Miles Franklin.
我想要自首
And I want to turn myself in.
但是我有一个条件
But I got one condition.
释放我的妻子
My wife, she goes free.
我的女儿需要她的母亲
My little daughter, she needs her mother.
我觉得我没必要和你做交易 富兰克林先生
I don't think I need to make a deal with you, Mr. Franklin.
如果我有你需要的东西呢？
And what if I got something you need?
你的妻子在一小时前被释放了
Your wife was released an hour ago.
她马上就会到这里来
She'll be here soon.
你要向我保证她会没事
You promise me that she will be okay.
只要你能完成交易
Just hold up your end of the deal.
我会的
I will.
我会把斯科菲尔德给你
I'll get you scofield.
走吧
Come on.
开始吧
Here we go.
你认为这是一段对话？
You think it's a conversation?
一段他们不想让我们听到的对话
One they don't want us hear.
准备好了吗？
You ready?
开始吧
Let's do it.